techdows.com 2019-06-16

# Privacy Policy

TechDows.com values our readers privacy.

Your privacy is critically important to us. At Techdows.com, we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone.
  * The only personal information we store is your IP address in order to make the site function.

We use your Personal Information for three primary purposes:

  * To help you quickly find services or information on the site.
  * To help us create and deliver content most relevant to you.
  * To serve advertisement.

 **Personal identification information**

We may collect personally identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, they need to enter name and email address to make a comment and to contact us. The IP addresses will be stored by server.

If you refuse to supply personal identification information such name , email address, then don’t make comment or don’t contact us.

 **Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information including IP address.

 **Cookies**

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web Site, and they may deploy cookies in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

 **Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

 **How Google uses data when you use our partners’ sites or apps**

Some of the services are served by Google on Techdows. Google uses its technology to serve ads to users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. Techdows uses the following Google services:

  * Google AdSense.
  * Google Analytics.

Your web browser automatically sends certain information to Google. This includes the URL of the page you’re visiting and your IP address.  
Please visit [Google’s privacy policy page](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/partner-sites/) to learn more about how it uses information from sites or apps that use their services.

 **Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others.

 **Where we send your data**

No, but visitors comments may be checked through automated spam detection service. We use WordPress commenting.

 **Changes to this privacy policy**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Techdows may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Techdows’s sole discretion. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

 **Who can I ask if I have any additional questions?**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement and our practices, or you have reason to believe Techdows may have failed to adhere to this Privacy Statement, you can contact us via email: techdows at gmail dotcom.
